19930
IMAP client does not use QRESYNC
Any modern IMAP client should be using QRESYNC rather than blindly refetching flags for all messages whenever it reselects a folder. See RFC5162.

19931
CA inclusion
I'm doing a research in which I try to find out what the requirements of Google are for putting a root CA at the trusted root list. This in the context of the current problems at Diginotar. To my suprise I couldn't find what is required to be put on that list by Google. This in contrast with other organisations that offer a webbrowser like Microsoft Apple Opera... All the requirements look te same to me but it would be nice if I could find a page that list these requirements. Is there a Google Root certification program? Once you are a trusted root does this count for all Google product (Android Chrome etc.)? Do you have a list with the trusted roots and a link to audit reports? Thanks in advance. Greetings Ivo PS. I have managed to found this page after a long search (@Google.nl obviously (A) ) and this link: http://groups.google.com/group/android-security-discuss/browse_thread/thread/9ff5d8cf5466e5d1

19934
Received Android 2.3.4 update to Droid Incredible and now Google accounts do not sync and Google Talk broken
Received the OTA upgrade to 2.3.4 yesterday morning. I subsequently have not successfully synced any of my Google products since which means I haven't been able to receive new Gmail update my calendar or contacts etc. Also Google Talk does not load. I click it and the sign-in screen flashes for a second then I'm back on the home screen. Also a few applications just randomly stopped working/disappeared. This needs to be addressed ASAP as my phone is now not nearly so useful. Device: Droid Incredible Carrier: Verizon Wireless Country / Language: USA - English OS / Browser / build number (if applicable): Android 2.3.4

19937
TrafficStats.getMobileRxBytes() and TrafficStats.getMobileTxBytes() reset very frequently on 3.0.1
The TrafficStats API TrafficStats.getMobileRxBytes() and TrafficStats.getMobileTxBytes() seem to be broken on Android 3.0.1 (I am using Galaxy Tab 10.1). TrafficStats.getMobileRxBytes() and TrafficStats.getMobileTxBytes() are used to monitor the data received and sent by the device over a cellular network. The values returned by these APIs are expected to increment as the device receives and sends data and reset only after a phone reboot. The behavior on my Android 2.2 and 2.3 phone is as expected the values returned by TrafficStats.getMobileRxBytes() and TrafficStats.getMobileTxBytes() keep increasing as the devices receives and sends cellular data. However on Android 3.0.1 (on my tablet) the values returned by TrafficStats.getMobileRxBytes() and TrafficStats.getMobileTxBytes() reset very frequently. This makes it impossible to monitor the cellular data consumption of the tablet. My Device Details are as follows: Model: Samsung Galaxy Tablet 10.1 Model Number: GT-P7100 Android Version: 3.0.1 Kernel Version: 2.6.36.3-00558-g7c1c334         se.infra@SEI-29#1] Build number: HRI83.BUKD9

19944
android arabic
we need arabic langugah in android plz goooooogle

19949
i9100 ringer and speaker issue
i am using samsung i 9100 sometime it s ringer speaker mic stop working and i have to restart phone to fix issues so kindly give me solution for that.

19960
Different Application instances for different processes in an app?
Application.onCreate() is called for every process inside an app.

19815
Samsung GIO. Official update from 2.2
Google searches shoew similair problmes on other devices and refer to a bug in GingerBread 2.3.3 Could you pls confirm it? And tell when it will be fixed?

19821
Shutter lag evo3d
The is a discernible shutter lag in taking pictures on the evo3d it is terrible.

19829
Access to Key board
- Steps to reproduce the problem (including sample code if appropriate). The steps are always the same; add a contact enter the number there is no way to get rid of the keyboard unless you tab in the email box (regardless if you want to enter an email. Then there is an option for the key board. - What happened. You cannot access the keyboard after you are done entering a phone number. - What you think the correct behavior should be. I should be able to get back to the keyboard without tapping into the email box. NOTE: This form is only for reporting bugs found in the Android system while developing Android applications. Use the Tools templates for issues with the developer tools. Please describe the problem in detail. Be sure to include: - Steps to reproduce the problem (including sample code if appropriate). - What happened. - What you think the correct behavior should be. Don't forget to mention which version of Android you're using and/or which device the problem appears on (model and Android version). Please also run "adb bugreport" and archive the output.